(Raj:)Oh, if it's even
the U.S. military.
(Raj:)It could be foreign military
pretending to be American.
(Howard:)You're right. We turn our
guidance system over to them,
(Howard:)next thing we know,
they're using it against us.
(Raj:)I also love the enemies
of America.
(Beverly:)Penny, I hope the example
of my failed marriage
(Beverly:)to Leonard's father
doesn't discourage you
(Beverly:)from the commitment
you've made to one another.
Oh, of course not.
(Beverly:)Although Alfred and I had a lot
more going for us than you two.
(Leonard:)Mom, please save something
for the toast.
(Mary:)So, Alfred, what is it
that you do for a living?
(Alfred:)Oh, I'm an anthropologist.
(Alfred:)I study ancient peoples
and cultures.
(Mary:)My goodness, so all the way
back to the Flood.
(laughing)
(Sheldon:)Don't laugh...
she wasn't joking.